PRANAV **MEHROTRA**

Data Analyst

• 22/90 Pheel Khana, Kanpur

mehrotrapranav240@gmail.com

PROFILE INFO

Organized & goal-driven individual with one year of experience in working with a leading data analytics & decision sciences company. Go-getter attitude which helps in driving results on multiple tasks with different levels of complexity. Passionate about implementing and launching new projects. Ability to translate business requirements into technical solutions. Looking to build a career for an entry-level job with a reputed firm driven by technology.

EXPERIENCE

August 2023 - March 2024

Mu Sigma I Bangalore

Data Analyst

- Participated in various cadences to understand client requirements and address their problem. Created a detailed guide to move towards the issue & then followed by performing EDA (Exploratory Data Analysis). Fabricated dashboard utilizing both historical & current data to track the KPIs. Presented findings and recommendations to stakeholders and Facilitating data driven decision making processes.
- Implemented an automated Tableau tool at a leading USA pharma giant to facilitate and assess Field Medical support for priority clinical trials. Integrated critical metrics such as Clinical Trial Interactions, Study Visit Reports, and Clinical Trial Sites to monitor and gauge the effectiveness of Field Medical initiatives in real-time. This initiative optimized resource allocation, enhanced communication with healthcare professionals, and contributed to improving clinical trial efficiency by addressing recruitment challenges and fostering stronger collaborations between Field Medical teams and healthcare providers.

February 2023- April 2023

Webixy Technologies, Kanpur

Intern

- Charge for European Region
- Shortlisted various small business by Evaluating needs of the Company
- Offered digital marketing solutions & app development options to them

PROJECT

- Personal Portfolio- Developing a ReactJS application with Tailwind CSS for a personal portfolio, demonstrating proficiency in modern web technologies
- To-do list- it is a plan for the day application which is utilized to follow your everyday undertakings and records in a coordinated way.
- · Guess Number- This is a game which we can play. We should simply figure on the off chance that it is correct we dominate the match assuming it is off-base we lose.
- Pick game- 2 player game where the players need to throw dice and hold the score first to arrive at 100 dominates the match.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2023 | SRM University

B.Tech - Computer Sciences

Attended a workshop on Android Development

Woodbine Gardenia School - Class-XII

Sheiling House School, Kanpur - Class-X

Attended a workshop on Cyber Security Delivered by Rakshit Tandon

SKILLS

- Web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJs, Tailwind CSS
- Programming languages -Python, Java, C, C++
- Business Intelligence: PowerBI, Figma
- Databases: SQL

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi